hubdoc.com 2018-11-06

# Hubdoc: Document Collection & Management Software | Hubdoc

Privacy Policy 

This Privacy Policy has been prepared by Hubdoc™ Inc. (“Hubdoc”). This Privacy Policy sets out the manner in which Hubdoc collects, uses, discloses and otherwise manages personal information. This Privacy Policy applies to the privacy practices on our website, www.hubdoc.com (the “Website”). 

If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at <https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request>

Collection & use of personal information 

We may collect your personal information when you: 

Register for the Website  

Add an account and request that we check your account, on your behalf, on a regular basis and/or on-demand  

Upload documents to the Website  

Email documents to the Website  

Subscribe to one of our newsletters  

Post on one of our blogs or forums  

Contact Us

You may be asked to provide certain personal information to sign up for our services, including your name and email address. The personal information collected during the registration process is used to manage your account with Hubdoc. 

You also have the option to submit the email addresses of colleagues or other contacts in order to invite them to access your Hubdoc account. When you submit this information, we will only use it for the specific reason for which it is provided. 

If you believe that one of your contacts has provided us with your personal information and you would like to request that it be removed from our database, please contact us at 

. 

We collect billing information such as credit card number and use this for billing purposes and to fulfill your orders. 

When you add a third party account to your profile, such as a utility or financial account, we collect your third party account credentials (such as your username or account number and password). We use this personal information to access your online third party accounts on a regular basis and/or on-demand and retrieve any available information to present to you in your mailbox, filing cabinet or elsewhere on the Website. For example, if you provide your login credentials for a third party utility site, we use this information to gather and file your utility bills on www.hubdoc.com. Please note that you may remove your third party account information from our Website whenever you wish. 

If you wish to subscribe to one of our newsletter(s), we may collect your name and email address to send the newsletter to you. If you would like to no longer receive these emails you may follow the unsubscribe instructions contained in each of the emails you receive. 

When you comment on our blog or other public forums, we may collect your name, email address as well as any comments, suggestions and other feedback you provide as postings. We may use your comments, suggestions or feedback to monitor and/or improve our product and service offerings and our Website. Please remember that any information that you provide in these comment areas is accessible to the public, and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose any personal information about yourself or anyone else. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at 

. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why. 

Disclosure of personal information 

We will not disclose, trade, rent, sell or otherwise transfer your personal information without your consent, except as otherwise set out herein. 

We may transfer (or otherwise make available) your personal information to third parties that provide services on our behalf. For example, we may use service providers to host our Website and send out email on our behalf.   
Your personal information may be maintained and processed by service providers in the U.S. or other foreign jurisdictions, and personal information may be accessed by law enforcement authorities in such jurisdictions. Service providers are provided with the information they need to perform their designated functions, and we do not authorize them to use or disclose personal information for their own marketing or other purposes. 

We may transfer any information we have about you as an asset in conjunction with a merger or sale (including transfers made as part of insolvency or bankruptcy proceedings). You will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information. 

In certain situations, Hubdoc may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements. 

Hubdoc and its service providers may provide your personal information in response to a search warrant or other legally valid inquiry or order, or to an investigative body in the case of a breach of an agreement or contravention of law, or as otherwise required or permitted by applicable Canadian, U.S. or other law. We may also disclose personal information where necessary for the establishment, exercise or a defence of legal claims, or as otherwise permitted by law. When we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request. 

Additional information about our website 

Hubdoc and our third party tracking-utility partners may generate certain non-identifying and aggregate data and store it in log files. This information may include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data. We may use this aggregated and non-identifying information to further enhance our services. We may combine this automatically collected log information with other information we collect about you. We do this to improve services we offer you, to improve marketing, analytics, or site functionality. 

Technologies such as: cookies, beacons, tags and scripts are used by Hubdoc and our partners [specify type e.g. marketing partners], affiliates, or analytics or service providers [specify type e.g. online customer support provider, etc]. These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis. 

We use cookies for to remember users’ settings (e.g. language preference) and for authentication. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some features or areas of our site may be limited. 

Third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on our website or to display advertising based upon your web browsing activity also use HTML5 to collect and store information. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5. 

We partner with a third party to either display advertising on our website or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partner may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on this website and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you interest-based ads, you may opt-out by clicking [here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/) Please note this does not opt you out of being served ads. You will continue to receive generic ads. 

You can log in to our site using sign-in services such as Facebook Connect or an Open ID provider. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign up form. Services like Facebook Connect give you the option to post information about your activities on this Web site to your profile page to share with others within your network. 

The Website may contain links to other sites that Hubdoc does not own or operate. Except as provided herein, we do not provide your personal information to these third parties without your consent. We provide these links as a convenience. The linked websites have separate and independent privacy statements, notices and terms of use, which we recommend you carefully review. We do not have any control over such websites, and therefore have no liability or responsibility for the linked websites’ personal information practices. 

Security of Personal Information 

We have implemented measures designed to help protect personal information in our custody and control. We maintain reasonable administrative, technical and physical safeguards in an effort to help protect against unauthorized access, use, modification and disclosure of personal information in our custody and control. When you provide us with sensitive information (such as your credit card number and your linked account credentials), we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). No collection or transmission of information over the Internet or other publicly accessible communications networks can be guaranteed to be fully secure, however, and therefore, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any such information. If you have any questions about security on our Website, you can contact us at the information at the end of this privacy policy. 

Social Media Feature 

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it. 

Access & Removal of Your Personal information 

Upon request Hubdoc will provide you with information about whether we hold any of your personal information. You have the right to access, update, correct, and delete inaccuracies in your personal information in our custody and control, subject to certain exceptions prescribed by law. You may request access, updating, corrections, or deletions of inaccuracies by contacting us at the contact information provided below or by logging into your account and making the applicable changes in your Profile. You may also request that we delete a third party account and we will cease collecting personal information from the third party account or your personal information and delete relevant account credentials. We will respond to your request to access within 30 days. 

We have personal information retention processes designed to retain personal information of our customers for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

Changes to this Privacy Policy 

This Privacy Policy may be updated periodically to reflect changes to our personal information practices. The revised Privacy Policy will be posted on the Website. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the email address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We strongly encourage you to review the Privacy Policy often for the latest information about personal information practices. 

Contact us 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the practices described herein, you may contact us at: 

or via postal mail at 1881 Yonge Street, Suite 712, Toronto, Ontario M4S 3C4. 

Last updated: **June 28, 2018**
